And.
We.
Were
busy in the world beneath the scene
were you doing were mysterious.
And were the most Martin unexplored by man
were these of the wonders of the Golden
of Mexico who won the
West Coast tomorrow to me
were.
Ruled this is
a sponge fisherman who has been. Read man
getting into the most dangerous of all
occupations the room.
One by one.
The.
Room
one.
When
the that's coming up the
the the the.
Rule
that.
One
that. That.
For or
one. In.
The new. Orleans.
Are Luu the blues.
Old girl you're.
Old.
Very smart but the square you go on I leave
the switch I was on my own and we're
going home we can't go home with an icy
cold pop I can hear them laugh when we
bring has got
a bitch in the auction my tickets don't we
need you to die blues got I'd like going
to you know just like a
shock second smell sponges
a mile away I diver will go out
and he won't come up until
a boat spoke with hundred dollar strength
and your god is right here on board all
rules well yeah. Who made
a home while. You're
a game. Room.
To New Year. Old. Hates to
hate pop punk vomit to.
Include the video. Eight
hundred and so poorly
so full of stuff but there was
a big smile on the first I didn't catch. A
lot. Was.
Missing. At all no I don't remember I
wonder if your. Forefathers
are very much what
I was always. Wanted to
join here I was watching
a whole big. Push with. Your
lens your money now you
want to run your life. On
a freebie one of those. Big
.
Holes. Like. I have a six
hundred dollars string I'm on
a deep water I might
already got the money. Go
ahead I go back to my kids. Get ready.
Ajax company. Seventeen
thousand five hundred.
Where you go that's what you get
it that's what we want to know.
About letting us into the sixty
we like it. Where did you get it
we went to that well. Nobody's going
to the twelve mile race at the
till my brother pinks that's where we went
right up to Pete's Marco when it's in
the water we went where or where plenty of
happened down top think tough pants fit
loose on you you think initially and
you too scared to where. I went.
If you went down. What does it look like.
You're looking at
a girl I died. That car
only. One chance like
an Asian cut short story but. Every.
Get tangled up until you think
you're never going to get out
of it. I'm going to have.
To push you off. I wouldn't go down there
again but all this punches in the world.
You're spend your money. You go
broke. You'll go down again.
On. This tour card on to
New York's finest company.
I'm on. The discovery I'm
trying to do. Right. I want
to tell you fine just.
Give me
a six hundred dollars dollars dollars
Are you kidding so. What are you doing
after all the work you did bring in
a man you're giving away money and I
want to survive we still were lucky
to get stuff my fears of I have.
YOUR BOTTOM LINE TO YOU
FOR YOU TO DO FOR ME.
Scratch your I saw you. Go they're
going to feel well I'm going to
involve. My boss. Skinflint I thought
is pretty good on probably part
is that I. Am totally. Going to get.
Paid it's going to belong in my family.
Thanks Tony and Mike. To
your views on.
The in.
The off.
So
it's sad to see him so
got this so
. THANK YOU
THANK YOU THANK.
The dad.
Thank you thank you. Thank.
You for.
So you could take your camera so I think.
I rewrote. It.
Ready the. World.
Know that or sit in the
day.
Already whereas
to already.
Today the all the
a race all
ready. You say old I'll be
ready shoulders shall
ready.
The drama the already
heard all of the During the day.
The City New Jersey are going to your farm
for the last thing I want to thank you
for good luck when I touch for it what it
cost you five bucks right all right but
the crew was the same but I thought of it
it's just the stuff of legend if you put
on it like
a girl her age. Now you got that
process where you break free from going up
north and it's like we go now we want to
get this. I don't know if I was
Mike at the precinct bridge was.
Going to. Go out we're going to come home
with one of these right where we're going
to pull the. Mike Mike Mike
a lot of punches what you're being you you
mean we're going to it's like what you
say. Twelve mile range. We're going to thank
you Mike was the matter with you might
get the one who's going to hurt me.
Who don't belong in the grave.
Don't you don't understand. How long
time ago before you bought your pa
they. Will come from an Englishman going
to Key West and they work that day.
You know all day long beach. And
a place to board up for everybody and we
don't have no it's not like now all the
bad news is no sponge left except in
deep water as well as my need for this
or blade. Love that song anguish
means whatever you want he's. Not.
Going to fix the blade with my kids if
they catch us they're not going to do
a good job why do you worry so much there
are ten thousand of them keep conduct
like we start before the sun comes up by
noon we have finished your day's work and
then when you find I get
a little monkey means hold which we
can hope if we're lucky if we're
lucky so when they got across then he the
fish oh bless the folks thinking how much
more like do we need I'm going to work
boss don't forget you promise I'm going to
find the most beautiful fund you ever saw
all you wanted for and you're going to
pay me and my I'm going to stop eating out
of first day when I don't get home and
get to watch while you
like that gold simply was
a very old girl valued.
At the engineer's too much knowledge.
Come up with my pen about I shall want to
touch but for I did not press six telling
I remember but up not particularly things
like what that was they were all I did
then if they don't mean I will please my
blood I be dead right now you can't scare
me I'm going down we'll see what I mean
well for your promise. Been gone
a week on going on here on those are the
ones we've got for mamma to work bottom
same as you you promised me Pa I know I
don't like my promise you can go down when
we work you can't do that I mean pop
you gave the award you said that much.
Everything around like
a bullet. In my. Pocket and. All
I I know like what you nor like
and he don't like just because
he likes of light some things get him off
he just finished feeding is going home
come on Reg I was out of. The
room.
Got
a clock about offensive of the
fact that he was past. The
the with. Who then
with old with the old.
Who's.
Old.
And coming to. The same
wanted want to look for.
What they don't. Want to
get it before they can one little
thing it would still guide work and.
For. The day they're going
to walk. Outside out.
The debate so far as the other
one marked because I was.
Offended by that.
Not funny don't shut the donkey just trying
to trip her up separate to the like you
say right what I tell you
I'm gonna be fine we
might respond to all why you not
only within the gun put it down.
Six whites that's what you got to break on
an opener to come into our water for you
to get that structure waters to
your cost a little bit like there's
a lot that week at work
your position makes
a song on your part of the place the next
time I bring it out of the water line
during our break that one of them lets go.
And I think we played. To get the same
thing.
During
a room. With
.
The the.
Big.
But that's got.
To stop.
But you get up to respect them for they
were both like was God help us then I was
attacked in
a hurry by the. Next day and I think that
I've also forgot to put that actually so
like you know I'm. Going
to throw parties I'll buy
a house. Some furniture tables chairs Oh.
No don't tell me that you're going to move
we're going to move in we're going to
get married it was. Really. Quite
a bit of maybe I forgot I can't remember
if you ask me I'm asking now why don't you
take my hand. When it's when you marry
me. When it will you marry me Suppose I
say no you can't. Do you love me no
I do yes I know you do and I love
you too much like I love one of my
brothers. You know that the Taliban stop.
Would you marry. If I said Yes I know
if I said well I feel yes I don't know
what to say but maybe if I get acquainted
with lots and lots of Floyd County make
up my mind what do I do what you are being
helped you can get acquainted with lots
and lots of girls I don't want lots
of girls to just watch. Very quickly.
I have to. Say maybe but
I think I'm too young.
Don't you think someone else has
that I don't want to get that.
I get the girl as they are they get to make
it all the nicer when together they are
all better let me have
for spend that share.
I hope like you said it was a comeback a
pop when we come across God it's like
a bunch of one doing
a good. Weekend prove anything.
But the cure there's ourselves.
This is the both.
The sponges I hear somebody
else say hi them someplace.
Mike what you want to do open and they
don't open everything is fun just
a lot they gone what you
want now I'm going to find
a fellow I'm going to see how
brave he is with all the R.
You go back to the boat song oh hey well
maybe you want to need somebody to carry
you up you like like haunted me like like
some so. OK We're going to get on that.
Thank you so many three. Find what good
would do if we got home with all dogs.
Just. Celebrated. With pride here for.
The Robert. We have come so
much for you for your call.
I may have. Was about
everything great before.
A room full of scared of three great.
Great I'm not counting him. Got a man get
a drink around here. Let's
get to the great mystery
you sure we don't bother you.
Well we might as well go away. I'm Thomas
race my two sons. This is Arnold that's
all the matter with the
axe I went to. The.
Young Greek pretty girl.
What's on your mind
what's on my mind sponges What do you
think. How you followed us we were
good we work and you take everything away
but no hard feelings. This time you'll
win next time way way you want to buy dance
with your daughter mystery. One of us
may have. Done it asked me. You might
have better luck if you ask me.
Then. Why not.
Go act like the old lady that maybe does
occur but as we go out Why don't you find
out the day oh well you better
be careful you might eat you up
a lot you won't even bother to
take off your hats I've got
a pretty good appetite myself you know you
might take away your lunch. I'm paying
for this girl's. Father. Records of life.
We're making elders but now I don't.
Do is
a complete free enterprise going to be
the biggest crowd that kid ever saw. I
don't want to grow this is
not. For me I'm after you.
Cut it down me. Sure and give me back my
head too short you always get what
people tell you to see a rapid
a kiss if they want to have crazy Greek how
you want to relate to this adult my mom
and I me after a Greek god I'm
a very beautiful young man why the whole
bunch of you must be crazy coming here you
know how called the law about
Greek woman to tell you how
a Greek feel about comps you're always
poking in the Glades Why don't you stay of
the line where you belong where you get
that line so we're going to log everybody
you've got a lot of nerve I
know one great that's got
a lot of nerve. I don't want to fight
all I want to do is hold hands.
A year from. Anybody ever tell you
a pretty. Well
you don't need that come on after the kids
got be glad to oblige you I have to have
no. Say I want to know
what you want to guy. He
just wants to bury me that's
gone he's too old for
a kid like you he must be at least
twenty five you've got to buy
a house if you find that we're going to
move to have lunch with any like the ones.
Here who do marry me and all your kids why
blue eyes I'll guarantee you personally
if you're real crazy. Kind
of can. It's all right.
We've been problematic. You're sure
you don't want to get. You know
what you mustn't. Let me
know if you change the mud.
Is my prison and it's law.
You're the only three.
Or four or.
Three.
Jim Tony don't hit up
the small is all mine
all clear now I'll see how big of
a man you are without the
ads I want to fight conch
style Greek style.
Hey stop it you know I don't like
your father you don't know my pop.
Where oh why do you think
your fellow down. Not
a very good biter without the
actual donate you kissed
a girl goodbye we go. Tony that's another
goodbye I was being how
did tonight like great.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh. Oh Oh precious Craig.
Oh. No.
Oh I gave up
a lot take the fight. Back. OK
now we go home. We're not going
home just. We're going out with
a twelve mile wave. Much. Like what
you expect obstacle going home with
an empty boat when we go home I go on I
was born here I pull over all and tsunami
we're going to have money. We're going to
basic what. I managed to do is work that
can't be scared all upon. God But Iraq.
Where.
The OR.
My God. I don't think it might. I
think about the one thing. I
promised it would work but I have.
I want to. Say I wanted to see.
That no I. Like water from. Here it. Has
a very breezy. I said yesterday. It was.
Down with. That but. All kinds
of space all the life is in the.
Video. As well as the.
Grass like in the fall. And what
that died of on. That crest.
Is down there full of sponges you have
never seen so many spines if you're going
and you if you're big on hold on
a million pounds on. A.
Fine you want down in deep
water. You get scared.
You don't know how scared you
can be. And I wanted. The real.
Reason now go bonkers. It went on.
And one day when you are not knocking.
It grabs you. Bonnie
I've been thinking about
a lot of things I'm going to work
while my ass. Off you promise me
you can hear more. And I know I. Know
you will die when the right time and
I'll miss. But you see I promise your mom
I said. I promise that I would take that
. As what you're going to stay is it's to.
You'll understand boy. Done
a. Bad
.
Rap there.
One
can.
Learn
. In
room.
Than.
Nine.
By.
Six by
a common one. The
one the
iron. Bar
where. The
Been.
Written.
One.
Why are the whining on the
line when I'm not the right one
the bomb on the bottom
line on the sideline
whine
whine whine.
Whine whine.
Whine. Whine.
Whine whine
whine not only about
what
the stuff that's got the government
that's not going to done in which you can
announce one thousand. One.
I. Saw.
Myself laugh at us but. My.
Money will go to pike and then I
started there and just clicked.
His allies psycho to light it up and got
the watch my back was going to pass went
back to what I said on the phone like
a bad. Bad idea about it
but they did not it's not.
That bad without the Bernhardt
bad when the guy gets stuck at.
Home. And if you're wondering
whether or not it's all.
Out over the phone Scott got there. My
thought was I don't see it and I second
time round. No drive around never make it
not quicker than going to keyword Rodeo
the fourth kept telling us fun
is both. Are you sure nine. Fun
voters where others are from sports that
we're learning. Some very bad I tell them
to have an I'm going where superficial
stuff I write like they're not facts Oh if
you were looking stuff I love and I'm going.
To hit my point when I buy things how
much will we like to bang
a lot of go I thank you none of that
there is just. One Beyond I can like
after. The.
Break both just came in like that and
that's not on board like it was her bad or
good job whoever was going to back
tonight or the ambulance comes
out of the crowd because
God was there till
she snipped off that he's like payouts on
the line also holds up like that speak
a couple of five five sloops it up please.
How is that is dead.
You'll have to moderate on with the
culture of God we want to know how this
happened. Bring along
a couple months. But I was always.
George cried Come with me.
You'll watch the boat.
With poor.
Old.
Globe for.
Luongo. Or with.
The or was.
No longer out.
Of the I. Know Our Whoa whoa
whoa. Whoa whoa whoa whoa.
Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa. Whoa forward.
To. The
hot. Spot.
It could be
a bit could do but so. How to be. Next
week vote back. And let me.
Say I will never learn. I will think.
Oh no.
Hey wait
a minute. And I think
these are our spot. Right
all right let's get out.
Why you're here right oh well go
run over and not get underway.
Anybody see how this fire started.
Out called it just. It was.
And. If you Michael one deployed. To
the point did you see who would line.
The Lord like Tony what
we're going to do now have.
An account or book on the topic yourself
that's what we're here for we'll give you
a total. Of almost so.
I thought you know what do you gun I'm not
going to get away with the law no what
you can't go Tony you'll come
with. Me But take it on faith.
I'm going to find out who did it I'm going
to get our spy just back I tell you No
you're coming with us to
study because your mama.
Done. You
should be walking around like this these
people will kill you you should have
stayed here you should have gone home I'd
like to talk to your father I've got
a feeling he's a reasonable man
look he's my father but he's
a con too I'm afraid to tell you everybody
around here looks up till you can make
get back our spikes where you live over in
friendship and it's when you're out to.
Tell me. A terrible thing about you.
Or something really awful Actually I don't
come here to the mysteries I came here
because I think you're
a fair man I used to think that creature
cos there was much difference between us I
was we live in this like this house but
what we do is the same as the work you do
when one of us dies you want to stand because
it's the same as if one of you ducked
but now I'm beginning to wonder I mean
somebody stole this fantasy that happened to
me. Who did.
He want you to help him what kind of
people live here anyway though they're not
respected and. They had to say.
You. Were on our birth father
was killed bringing up
those points is like driving again.
We didn't know we saw the boat
we didn't know it didn't start out faster
we don't know if you give it back we have
got to get back when long on the other
thought right in the boat they all OK I
always got was one string when I
saw the body he thought that.
Just think I know but
are you going to I'm going to fly along or
I'm the kind to keep what I get just by
more trouble because if you want to help
me given the body you've got the question
why aren't we have
a mind that we get that back in
the dark my head I caught him on
a dead. Grass
back.
Well. On the bike to keep where he's got
it doesn't matter anyway because we're going
to one tomorrow morning out of one of
your. Finest fishing or sometimes
I want to do you see and watch
if you have
a place to stay want to sleep here tonight
I'll be OK I'll see in the morning night
.
I don't like to came back it's not
the money that's important it's
what you do for yourself the one question
is not asked Arnold you've got to
remember that you're a man of that great
because only a boy or a woman has
a soft spot for
a boy it's better than when it feels far
but your jealousy makes something else out
of the pity how in the great comes tomorrow
morning will give an accounting you can
hand in the money yourself clever like that
won't be here tomorrow morning. Pathak
and that's the other guy.
That I.
Went to.
The boss.
Going to. Miami there's
a lady you know. Well it's
a grammar. But at.
The girl.
Girl.
Thank you.
Thank.
You.
The the little.
One.
One. I told you in the
trouble trying to help me I don't care
they burned your boat Well now you've got
a problem I don't know how to work hard
both What's not hard you can work or not
that sounds good got to go
deeper good sponsor me with
a diving suit an air pump. Sure we can see
why the equipment let you know cloud up
that part of the work all we need is one
load up the reason we can fix up the twelve
mile race Sure why don't the glades the
rigs only chance if you ever been down
before you sure Pop taught me how to wear
the suit the Bain attacks on Tony I'm too
scared to return dangerous I'm scared to
schedule can be but you forget one of you
can ever imagine how beautiful it is down
there's all kinds of fish and when they
get used to you they come right up your
face when you're looking you can feed
them just like they were pets they even
nibble right you think and then
there's every right corner
like
a garden full of flowers the deeper you
go the more beautiful it is like to dance
you are going to church after
just you don't want to come out
hey I was forgot where I agree
OK come on please. See.
When the whole when the whole with.
Old.
Girl. In
The Whole World War. Two more
with. The. Hands.
Of. The and the.
Little one. Little.
Little Ann Lou. Lou
with them the old of
a loner the old the.
Old age. To.
The old man.
Why the
one.
Who put up with the it was
the scouts first past the
pay that was not the just little thing
right they almost or just sail is hardly
ever. Done is missing one will
pass plays that are no could help
and it's not a. White
board are well there's
a lot of that test. Just
you'll find out why they call it calling.
Hey that's really good your mama sure
showed you all she did tell me I never knew
my mother she died when I was born.
When.
The was.
Like the most. Minute ago he
was like is not what we think
but your father your brother. The one you
help when you turn against them as I
WOULD you were thinking.
That I could say well that's
all you are you're just
a kid on lookers talk to. You know all I
have to do is yell in your life you know
thank you hope.
You're going to all of my. Folks on the.
Spot. They'll watch because I.
Always get up and I go up don't
you want to go make me whole.
Or are.
All.
The old.
Mom I was awfully worried about you we all
went to this is my sister Pat.
It's about time you come back
where you been with great stuff and happen
to you I got fed up she brought me home
you know Michael. Was Mama you got
the cemetery every day should
I have got to go to take
a penny. The
little. Girl in the. World looked
up at the home you have here.
You know they had your own.
You don't belong here you
belong home. I've read
all my life. Since I met the pope
but wait for him to come home
I know his God has never come back.
The BE. The the.
OP would like it if you knew you
write. A good man. You know how many
get. You'd want to go in just
like you. Know like we've got to
come on. Let's go.
Have a so. In that paper had
a founding father. Of Attorney Brad.
You know uprooted who she is she's
done the skunk got us from Key West
you want to hear NY mom her
name is going to prison
a Hi Tony go ahead tell you mama what you
want to do the way I tell you he's gets
booked he's going to walk splodge like to
come out of the boys will bring in one
load and we'll fix up the ugly
kid that listed how he talked to
a little boy girl you're going to do this
Tony all by yourself if if with your
public here you go I'm here so what's the
matter with me oh don't be angry County
it was not my Tony I like you
you could go for
a long time if you love him you don't let
him do it every time he goes out you're
going to die every night you wait all by
yourself like I wait you're going to be
scared like. You'll see my
thank you to my house for
a big scare listen to
you you'll tell him no
sure you're scared I'm scared too but you
can't be scared all your life we've got
a boat we're going to work
that's what you want is
a plumber Joe Madison around the house
hanging my head he has to get what he wants
to get cancer understand I can't
tell him what to do nobody
might as well make up your mind mama.
When we go. Right away
we'll start writing out
a more. Oh Bubba talk to me hard
What do you want me to say well say
something like money like like what
we got the. I project you come
a long way that I pick something for
you your way I think when you take
my mama's cook.
That's not that even so I need no diving
so no diving so it needs money whether you
come out of that money. While you
look at it don't let your smoke from
a cigar that you want to make
a little but. The
point how much money you you know you got
all enough things Dorney all part of
a burden to when you farm or die or get
somebody saying goodbye where do you get
that stuff. I owe you
a lot of money I can feel it coming my
neck I'm one of them dollars ready for war
a little less twelve dollars and I don't
know well we're going to pay you back
every cent what you think of that or I'm
glad to see you make me short have it
before your very words are bought
a little more and I believe you deserve
us through through what you've read or I
want to hear you know. Who
said anything about money from
a producer our war critic I'm sure when
someone wants to borrow or when you don't
want any money what if your wife
both of you and I go one for
a lot and. All we want to do it always
was exciting so if you had plenty just
give us what they thought was nothing all
day was easy to dive into but all there
was. A call our talk ironic because
you were not going off. Are
you guys really cool.
That works OK. But the night the sun is.
Real That's what we're.
Going to you're going to die going to
work and thoughtful want to go to. A good
start just got everything OK.
Depend we're ready to
leave. It's going to be
a rough look you don't know how to have
a look hopefully I can help you be on
the way. To be with you when you can.
Please.
Take.
My mama.
It was told to take
a backward vote for the pointer
we call them knowing. When
to give me the slip if I am alone cast you
stood up for you you stood up for the
Greek and yet tried to give them money so
you both know it got their daughter in
the grave All right it was
wrong or they are were fine
bring going to back you good
kids and you'll never forget.
I'm. Not you know me.
I don't think I would think. Most
modest or get another set is that.
You know you know put them if you don't
want to what I'm going to. When I say no
I'm the guy right so yeah. Come on
finish reading me come on with.
So many voices you know everything I know
if I can only put in you and I have to
find out for myself.
By.
The
or wrong
the
wrong. One.
Bomb.
Bomb one.
One the wrong.
The saw
a. Whopping
one.
The wrong.
The bomb
when the
dawn.
The dog
when the
bomb the. The
or or.
The.
I Phone up.
To the phone to the same job.
That.
Why not come up then I
don't like like I call.
It Like It's all come up.
Feels like with this concert
I get more clockwork that's.
Why you will come up when
I give the season as
well as others. Like I
got product. What I got
out. Honey what's past my
life I guess what about my
head get out of the case.
Scared I was petrified I said.
I tell you what excites. Me.
Right. Here.
So what the. Little.
Organ for the great. But. By now you know.
Seven further inquiry. Along that go
aboard. They're about to get down.
I'm up and down on the payback.
My final year down there oh I have to.
Come on when I. Come off.
Are you with us or with you. I'm with you.
I mean why.
Are don't be mad Mr Rhys you think
she's just a kid that we're both
a couple like us but we're not kids anymore
is no good to fight you know maybe she
is married to
a great but she's still your
daughter will be in. Go to become. A
What's the matter there. Are
Still that we've got for
a subtle but don't attract have
a budget over the web. Site
. Baby.
Girl gotta go to Burger.
Mom that is.
So the. Law.